[Music]
for a country that predominately favors
debit cards a whopping 27 percent growth
in the credit card market last year
turned heads in the financial world
ICICI Bank wanted to act quickly
on the new opportunities presented by
retail Bollywood however there was one
roadblock the cost of acquiring new high
quality leaders we set out to optimize
customer acquisition with a combination
of proprietary machine learning tools
Facebook's ability to provide deep user
insights and campaign data made of the
ideal platform a thorough analysis of
potential customers enabled us to
identify segments with lower cost per
acquisition then we deployed two
automated tools to deliver relevant ads
to our Joseph's audience I creative and
I capture - proprietary tools built by
solution labs for you I created was used
for creating customized ads where as I
capture was used to develop personalized
nothing pages this enabled a holistic
marketing campaign that displayed the
right credit card offers the right
people based on their entrances
to amplify the effectiveness of our
campaign or third proprietary tool
budget optimizer was utilized analyzing
campaign data our budget optimizer
reallocated the budget to different
segments based on that overall
performance further reducing the cost
per acquisition the tag based solution
was a success the cost per application
reduced by 50% while the cost per
eligible lead degrees by 43% this
resulted in a substantial reduction of
cost per credit card by 38%
month-on-month for ICICI Bank
[Music]